BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XVIII: Code #61, Educational Services
  - Code no.800372: Racine Unified School District and National Education Association; Racine Educational Association, 1990- 1993 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Item 2: Racine United School District, Board of Education and Racine Education Association, 1992-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 8/25/1992 and expires on 8/30/1993. Covers 1540 workers in Racine, WI
  - Code no.800389: Wisconsin, State of and Teaching Assistant's Association, 1991-1993 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: State of Wisconsin and Teaching Assistants' Association, 1991-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1991 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 2400 workers in Madison, WI
    - Item 2: State of Wisconsin and Teaching Assistants' Association, 1991-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1991 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 2193 workers in Madison, WI
  - Code no.820790: Baltimore Board of Education and Teachers Association, 1981-1989 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Independent School District No. 625, Saint Paul, Minnesota, Board of Education and Teachers Association of Baltimore County, Maryland, Inc., 1981-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1981 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 6300 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 2: Baltimore County, Board of Education of and Teachers Association of Baltimore County, Maryland, Inc., 1982-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers 5200 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 3: Baltimore County, Board of Education of and Teachers Association of Baltimore County, Maryland, Inc. Supplement, 1982-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers an unknown number of workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 4: Baltimore County, Board of Education and Teachers Association of Baltimore County, Maryland, Inc., 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1984 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers 6100 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 5: Baltimore County, Board of Education and Teachers Association of Baltimore County, Maryland, Inc., 1987-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1987 and expires on 6/30/1988. Covers 6200 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 6: Baltimore County, Board of Education and Teachers Association of Baltimore County, Maryland, Inc., 1988-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1988 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 6000 workers in Baltimore, MD
  - Code no.820815: Clark County School District and Clark County Classroom Teachers Association, 1985-1989 (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Clark County School District and Clark County Classroom Teachers Association, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 8/27/1985 and expires on 1/1/1987. Covers 4950 workers in Las Vegas, NV
    - Item 2: Clark County School District and Clark County Classroom Teachers Association, 1987-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 8/27/1987 and expires on 1/1/1989. Covers 5300 workers in Las Vegas, NV
  - Code no.820816: Clark County School District and Education Support Employees Association, 1985-1995 (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Clark County School District and Classified School Employees Association of Clark County, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 8/8/1985 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers 3240 workers in Las Vegas, NV
    - Item 2: Clark County School District and Classified School Employees Association of Clark County, 1987-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 11/18/1987 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 3450 workers in Las Vegas, NV
    - Item 3: Clark County School District and Classified School Employees Association of Clark County Addendum, 1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 9/2/1988. Covers an unknown number of workers in Las Vegas, NV
    - Item 4: Clark County School District and Education Support Employees Association of Clark County, 1993-1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 12/7/1993 and expires on 6/30/1995. Covers 5286 workers in Las Vegas, NV
  - Code no.820825: Pasco County District School Board and United School Employees of Pasco County, 1987-1996 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Pasco County, District School Board and United School Employees of Pasco, 1987-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 11/17/1987 and expires on 6/30/1990. Covers 1450 workers in Pasco Co., FL
    - Item 2: Pasco County, District School Board and United School Employees of Pasco, 1992-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 11/10/1992 and expires on 6/30/1996. Covers 1815 workers in Pasco Co., FL
    - Item 3: Pasco County, District School Board and United School Employees of Pasco, 1994-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1994 and expires on 6/30/1996. Covers 1900 workers in Pasco Co., FL
    - Item 4: Pasco County, District School Board and United School Employees of Pasco Memorandum, 1995; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 8/28/1995. Covers 1900 workers in Pasco Co., FL
    - Item 5: Pasco County, District School Board and United School Employees of Pasco Addendum, 1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1996. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pasco Co., FL
  - Code no.820832: North Shore School District and National Education Association, 1991-1996 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Northshore School District and Northshore Education Association Memorandum, 1991-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1991 and expires on 8/31/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in King Co., WA
    - Item 2: Northshore School District No. 417 and Northshore Education Association, 1991-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1991 and expires on 8/31/1994. Covers 1070 workers in King Co., WA
    - Item 3: Northshore School District No. 417 and Northshore Education Association, 1994-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1994 and expires on 8/31/1996. Covers 1170 workers in King Co., WA
    - Item 4: Northshore School District No. 417 and Northshore Education Association, 1995-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1995 and expires on 8/31/1996. Covers an unknown number of workers in King Co., WA
  - Code no.820836: Sweetwater Union High School District and State Educational Association; National Education Association, 1985- 1993 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Sweetwater Union High School District, Board of Trustees and Sweetwater Education Association/CTA/NEA, 1985-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 9/27/1985 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 1465 workers in Chula Vista, CA
    - Item 2: Sweetwater Union High School District, Board of Trustees and Sweetwater Education Association/CTA/NEA, 1991-1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 178, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 4/11/1991 and expires on 6/30/1993. Covers 1400 workers in Chula Vista, CA
  - Code no.830038: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and American Federation of Teachers, 1978-1994 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 400, 1978-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1978 and expires on 8/31/1980. Covers 3580 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 2: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 400, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1980 and expires on 9/4/1983. Covers 3500 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 3: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 400, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/5/1983 and expires on 8/31/1986. Covers 3150 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 4: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 400, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1985 and expires on 9/4/1988. Covers 3069 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 5: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 400, 1988-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/5/1988 and expires on 9/6/1992. Covers 3000 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 6: Pittsburgh Board of Public Education and Pittsburgh Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 400 Addendum, 1992-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 9/7/1992 and expires on 12/31/1994. Covers 3000 workers in Pittsburgh, PA
  - Code no.830044: Philadelphia Board of Education and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, 1978-1992 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Philadelphia School District and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 3, 1978-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1978 and expires on 8/31/1980. Covers 17000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 2: Philadelphia School District and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 3, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1980 and expires on 8/31/1982. Covers 18000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 3: Philadelphia School District and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 3, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1982 and expires on 8/31/1985. Covers 13300 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 4: Philadelphia School District Board of Education and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 3 Memorandum, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1985 and expires on 8/31/1988. Covers 20000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 5: Philadelphia School District and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 3, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Item 6: Philadelphia School District and Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 3 Memorandum, 1988-1992; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 2)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1988 and expires on 8/31/1992. Covers 19000 workers in Philadelphia, PA
  - Code no.830150: Detroit Board of Education and American Federation of Teachers, 1977-1990 (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: City of Detroit School District Board of Education and Detroit Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 231, 1977-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1977 and expires on 7/2/1979. Covers an unknown number of workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 2: City of Detroit School District Board of Education and Detroit Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 231, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1979 and expires on 7/1/1982. Covers 11000 workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 3: City of Detroit School District Board of Education and Detroit Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 231, 1982-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 7/1/1983. Covers 11000 workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 4: City of Detroit School District Board of Education and Detroit Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 231, 1983-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1983 and expires on 6/30/1985. Covers 11500 workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 5: City of Detroit School District Board of Education and Detroit Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 231, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 6/30/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Detroit, MI
    - Item 6: City of Detroit School District Board of Educationand Detroit Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 231, 1987-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 3)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1987 and expires on 6/30/1990. Covers 10000 workers in Detroit, MI
  - Code no.830189: New York City Board of Education and AFL-CIO, 1978-1984 (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: City of New York School District Board of Education and Board of Education Employees, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 372, 1978-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1978 and expires on 6/30/1980. Covers 900 workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: City of New York School District Board of Education and Board of Education Employees, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 372, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 3: City of New York School District Board of Education and Board of Education Employees, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, Local 372, 1982-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 4)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers 1000 workers in New York, NY
  - Code no.830205: Milwaukee Public Schools and Service Employees International Union, 1977-1994 (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Milwaukee Board of School Directors and Service and Hospital Employees' International Union, Local 150, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1977 and expires on 6/30/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 2: Milwaukee Board of School Directors and Service and Hospital Employees' International Union, Local 150, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1983. Covers 1100 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 3: Milwaukee Board of School Directors and Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 150, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1983 and expires on 6/30/1986. Covers 900 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 4: Milwaukee Board of School Directors and Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 150, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1986 and expires on 6/30/1989. Covers 1050 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 5: Milwaukee Board of School Directors and Service Employees' International Union, AFL-CIO, Local 150, 1992-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 5)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1992 and expires on 6/30/1994. Covers 1000 workers in Milwaukee, WI
  - Code no.830212: Baltimore, City of and American Federation of Teachers, 1978-1993 (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Board of School Commissioners and United Teachers of Baltimore City, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1978-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1978 and expires on 8/31/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 2: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1980 and expires on 6/30/1982. Covers 1760 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 3: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1982-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1982 and expires on 6/30/1984. Covers 1600 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 4: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1984-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1984 and expires on 6/30/1986. Covers 1600 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 5: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1986-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1986 and expires on 6/30/1988. Covers 1600 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 6: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1986-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Item 7: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340, 1988-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1988 and expires on 6/30/1990. Covers 1650 workers in Baltimore, MD
    - Item 8: City of Baltimore and Baltimore Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 340 Addendum, 1993; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1993. Covers an unknown number of workers in Baltimore, MD
  - Code no.830222: Gary Community School Corp. and American Federation of Teachers, 1981-1987 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Gary Board of School Trustees and Gary Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, Local 4, 1981-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1981 and expires on 12/31/1981. Covers an unknown number of workers in Gary, IN
    - Item 2: Gary Board of School Trustees and Gary Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, Local 4, 1982-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1982 and expires on 12/31/1982. Covers an unknown number of workers in Gary, IN
    - Item 3: Gary Board of School Trustees and Gary Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, Local 4, 1983-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1983 and expires on 12/31/1983. Covers an unknown number of workers in Gary, IN
    - Item 4: Gary Board of School Trustees and Gary Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, Local 4, 1984-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1984 and expires on 12/31/1984. Covers an unknown number of workers in Gary, IN
    - Item 5: Gary Board of School Trustees and Gary Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, Local 4, 1986-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1986 and expires on 12/31/1987. Covers an unknown number of workers in Gary, IN
  - Code no.830223: Chicago Teachers Union and AFL-CIO, 1981-1987 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1981-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1981 and expires on 8/31/1982. Covers 28000 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 2: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1982-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1982 and expires on 8/31/1983. Covers 25100 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 3: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1983-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1983 and expires on 8/31/1984. Covers 27350 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 4: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1984-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1984 and expires on 8/31/1985. Covers 28200 workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 5: Chicago Board of Education and Chicago Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 1, 1985-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1985 and expires on 8/31/1987. Covers 28800 workers in Chicago, IL
  - Code no.830228: Grand Rapids Public School and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1977-1994 (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Grand Rapids Public Schools Board of Education of the and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1977 and expires on 8/31/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Grand Rapids, MI
    - Item 2: Grand Rapids Public Schools Board of Education and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1980-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1980 and expires on 8/31/1982. Covers 2100 workers in Grand Rapids, MI
    - Item 3: Grand Rapids Public Schools Board of Education and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1982-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 11/3/1982 and expires on 8/31/1984. Covers 2100 workers in Grand Rapids, MI
    - Item 4: Grand Rapids Public Schools Board of Education and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1984-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1984 and expires on 8/31/1986. Covers 1800 workers in Grand Rapids, MI
    - Item 5: Grand Rapids Public Schools Board of Education and Grand Rapids Education Association, 1992-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1992 and expires on 8/31/1994. Covers 1735 workers in Grand Rapids, MI
  - Code no.830255: Boston School Committee and American Federation of Teachers, 1978-1992 (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 66, 1978-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1978 and expires on 8/31/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Boston, MA
    - Item 2: Boston School Committee and Boston Teachers Union, American Federation of Teachers, AFL-CIO, Local 66, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 179, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1980 and expires on 8/31/1983. Covers an unknown number of workers in Boston, MA